# LEXIS VON SEGGERN

**■** lexisvons@gmail.com **♦** 402-720-9762

lexisvon
in lexisvonseggern

**y** lexisvon **⊕** personal-website

# **AFFILIATIONS**

AIGA SCC Student Group Director of Programing Co-Chair January - June 2017

> AIGA NE Member April 2016 to current

#### **VOLUNTEER WORK**

AAF Addys Judging 2017 Do Space / Teaching 2017

#### **SKILLS**

#### **PROFICIENT**

Sketch
Adobe CC Applications/
InDesign
Illustrator
Photoshop
Dreamweaver

Mac and Windows OS

# KNOWLEDGE

HTML/HTML 5

CSS3 SASS Responsive Web Dev. Sublime Text Java Script Slack

Toggl Trello

#### **FAMILIAR**

Ruby Bootstrap Wordpress Invision Customer Service Team Player Time Management Organized

#### BIO

A motivated graphic designer, passionate and knowledgeable about innovative user interface design, user experience, front-end web development, and responsive design, with a minimal style. Provides support in customer satisfaction through the workplace and excels in meeting deadlines on projects by having time management and organizational skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **SOUTHEAST COMMUNITY COLLEGE**

Associates of Applied Sciences

Lincoln, NE Graduated June 2017

# **OMAHA CODE SCHOOL**

Front-End Development
Omaha, NE
Graduation Oct 2017

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **SALES ASSOCIATE**

JcPenny's

Lincoln, Nebraska

August 2015 to June 2016

Provided customer service by helping customers in the store, managed the cash register, and placed online orders.

# MANAGER/LIFEGUARD

**Hooper Swimming Pool** 

Hooper, Nebraska

May 2013 to August 2015

Managed the pool, ordered chemicals, handled money, ran swimming lessons, and created operational hours.

# **PROJECTS**

# THE NORMANDY

The Normandy is a French cuisine restaurant that focuses on fine dining, located in Lincoln Nebraska. This responsive website enhances their high-end atmosphere and style through minimal, refined typography, beautiful photos, and an interactive menu.

# LEXISVON.COM

An idea for my own personal website to display some of my work. Designed to reflect my love of a minimal style with lots of white space and simple navigation.

#### **BEAUTY BAR**

Beauty Bar is a cool nightclub that was transformed into a luxurious, swanky time capsule of big hair, pink nails, and dry martinis. This is a conceptual design for the new website to attract and show people what Beauty Bar is all about.